enow.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy policy on AOL Answers.

This document contains information regarding our privacy policy and practice and is brought to you so you feel comfortable using our website and services. It is presented for your benefit and describes how we collect and use information. Please take a minute to read the following statement in order to make sure you agree with our practices. By using AOL Answers, you permit the usage of your Personal Information and User Generated Content (as such terms are defined below) as outlined below in our Privacy Policy and in the Terms of Use. 

AOL Answers highly respects your privacy and takes special measures to help insure that any personal information collected by us is used solely in accordance with our privacy policy. It is important for us that you understand both what kind of information is collected and how it is used. 

As part of the services granted by this website, people using AOL Answers may exchange knowledge, provide information, reviews, and opinions on various topics of discussion contained herein. In order to fulfill the purposes of our site we need to display a limited amount of personal identifying information to be provided by the people using AOL Answers, which ultimately is intended so that other people may evaluate the trustworthiness of the information provided herein. 

At the outset of joining the services provided in this website, you will be prompted to provide certain registration information, in order for us to be able to identify and/or contact you regarding our services and/or products. Such prompted information may include your first and last name, nickname or User IDs from our affiliates (e.g, AOL, ICQ), mailing address, e-mail address, Instant Messenger ID, birth date, and certain location information such as city, state, and/or zip code, as well as other information that you may elect to provide to us such as gender, blog or web site address, topics of interest and knowledge, and user names that you use on other social networking sites that you may wish to share on AOL Answers ( **"Personal Information"** ). Kindly note that Personal Information may also include certain information which is not explicitly submitted by you, as we log your browser-type related information, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp. 

As opposed to Personal Information which you may be prompted by AOL Answers to provide, when using the services provided by our website, which, primarily, is intended for voluntary sharing and transferring of information, you shall be free to provide (subject to the Terms of Use) any kind of non-abusive information of your choice, such as questions on various topics, answers to other people' questions, your profile photo, images of your choice, video reviews, ratings, and any other kind of content you voluntarily choose to provide ( **"User Generated Content"** ). 

**AOL Answers will not sell, provide, rent, trade, or otherwise share your Personal Information with or to third parties for their promotional use** , except as required by subpoena, search warrant or other legal process or in the case where failure to disclose information will lead to imminent harm to customers or others. Please note however that we may use your email address to send you updates or news regarding our site, but you may choose not to receive emails of this type by updating your notification settings here. 

AOL Answers may use agents, corporate affiliates and contractors in order to help operate AOL Answers. If such agents and contractors have access to Personal Information, they are required to protect this information in a matter that is consistent with the Privacy Policy and may use such information solely for providing the AOL Answers services. 

Please note that use of User Generated Content in this Website is made according to Creative Commons licensing methods. Such User Generated Content will be posted on publicly available areas on AOL Answers and can be viewed and used by others on the AOL Answers website and the websites of AOL Answers’s authorized distributors in accordance with our Terms of Use. For further information on the way in which your User Generated Content may be used please refer to our Terms of Use. 

Due to the nature of the web and the public nature of AOL Answers please be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g., sign in name, e-mail address) via posts, messages, forums, etc., such information, along with any substantive information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and used by third parties for various purposes, including unsolicited messages from such third parties, and such activities are beyond the control of AOL Answers. Please do not include in your User Generated Content any information which you wish to keep private. 

As we are committed to protecting the security of your Personal Information AOL Answers uses various security technologies and means in order to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. 

As suppliers of downloads we naturally acknowledge the negative impact spyware has had on the internet, as after being infected with spyware, people are less likely to download and try new software. AOL Answers cannot guarantee that downloads which were not created by AOL Answers shall be free from spyware, AOL Answers nonetheless shall use reasonable efforts to prevent the inclusion of spyware in downloads created/provided by third parties. 

Upon your first visit to AOL Answers, a cookie is sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. A "cookie" is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. We use [cookies](http://about.aol.com/aolnetwork/beacons) to improve the quality of our service and to better understand how people interact with us. Please also note that our advertisers may also place or recognize cookies on your browsers. 

AOL Answers and its advertisers may use ad network providers and other service providers to help present customized content and advertisements on AOL Answers and other Web sites. These providers may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies on your computer to help present, better target, and measure the effectiveness of their content and advertisements, using data gathered over time and across their networks of Web pages to determine or predict the characteristics and preferences of their audience. AOL Answers may share certain non-personally identifiable information about you as a AOL Answers user (such as user age and zip code) with certain ad network and service providers to help them deliver more relevant content and advertisements through their networks. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by content and ad network providers is subject to their own privacy policies, not AOL Answers's. [Click here](http://about.aol.com/aolnetwork/beacons) to learn more about third party content and ad network providers and the choices you have about these technologies.

Although most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent, and you can also easily remove any cookie sent to you from our website. 

You have the right to access, correct and/or remove your Personal Information and privacy preferences at any time by using the AOL Answers Settings page. 

If you request the removal of your Personal Information, AOL Answers will use commercially reasonable efforts to functionally remove you and your Personal Information from the site; however, please be aware that it may be technically impossible to remove your Personal Information without some residual information being retained by AOL Answers. 

This Web Site is a general audience website and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 18. 

The Web Site may contain links to third party websites. AOL Answers is not responsible for the privacy practices of these websites, nor will AOL Answers be liable for any content related claim arising from visiting such third party websites. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp)

AOL Answers may from time to time update this privacy policy. When we make these updates, the "last updated" date listed on this policy will be changed accordingly. If a material change will be made in this statement, which affects your rights, AOL Answers will notify people using the service by placing a more prominent notice on our home page. 

If you believe that AOL Answers has not complied with this privacy policy with respect to your Personal Information or if you have other related inquiries or concerns, please feel free to write us at [admin@aolanswers.com](mailto:admin@aolanswers.com). 

This privacy policy shall be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the laws of the State of New York, without giving effect to its conflict of laws provisions, and any action arising from or related to this privacy policy and the use of our Web Site shall be brought only before the courts of New York, New York. 

Copyright

All rights reserved. © 2009 

Yedda Inc an AOL Company
